Guide to the Gerald Stern Papers, 1920s-2012 SC.2007.04
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Media Material, 1970-2007; XII.
  - Interviews and Lectures, 3.
    - Audiocassettes (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Compact Disks (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Videocassettes, 4.
    - 1980-2000 (Box 44, Folder 1)